Kouki-kun!
Let's go.
Let's stay a bit!
You should be in bed already.
I'm not even tired yet!
Kouki-kun, let's go!
All right, let's head home.
You go on ahead!
Shall I take you somewhere nice?
Somewhere nice?
Can we take a small detour?
Sure.
Man, you're heavy!
Don't hurt him!
Do you even have a fish tank at home?
No. But we have the bathtub!
You can't do that!
When you get home, put some tap water in a bucket and set it out on the veranda.
Why?
Because tap water has chlorine and stuff in it.
Here we go!
Rin-chan.
Hold still.
Take a look!
Hey!
We're gonna leave you behind!
Don't hurt him!
Shall we?
Yep!
This is the place.
Ah, a river!
I'm coming too!
There are places like this nearby, huh?
Is this the first time you've brought Rin-chan here?
Yeah. It's my first summer with her, after all.
It's too dark. I can't see anything!
Daikichi, tell us where to look.
Check over that way.
Let's go!
W-Wait!
It's already evening,
but it seemed like they wanted to keep playing.
Sounds like someone else we know.
Okay, we're this way, Kouki.
Goodnight.
See ya later!
Goodnight!
Shall we get going?
You've become taller.
「The Way Home」